<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Geekdocs</title><link>http://localhost/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Geekdocs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 17:42:07 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glossary</title><link>http://localhost/posts/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 17:16:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/glossary/</guid><description>AD - Active Directory - local database that contains all information.
ADSI - Active Directory Service Interfaces
AM - Access Management
API - Application Programming Interface
Attribute - specific criteria provided by the managed systems to describe the expected assignments for an identity.
Bastion - element used like an intermediary so that an administrator connects to bastion when they need sensitive access. It allows action tracking.
Claim - value for a given identity such as email, last name, groups, etc.</description></item><item><title>IGA and USERCUBE by Nicolas</title><link>http://localhost/posts/IGA/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 16:52:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/IGA/</guid><description>IAM / IAG IGA -Identity Governance and Administration- is a combination of IAM and IAG.
IAM -Identity Access Management- allows identities to have the right rights at the right time for the right reasons.
IAG -Identity Access Governance- allows actors to follow the developments concerning identities and user access, and monitor compliance.
Gartner is a form that means to give expert guidance and tools to enable smarter and faster decisions and stronger performance on an organization&amp;rsquo;s most critical priorities.</description></item><item><title>Introduction Guide</title><link>http://localhost/posts/Introduction-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 17:42:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/Introduction-guide/</guid><description>Overview Usercube is a three-aim solution for IGA.
Aim 1 - Manage Identity Lifecycle Usercube builds a reliable directory of identities and manages their evolution. An identity can be an employee, contractor, partner, customer, object, software, robot.
Aim 2 - Provide Entitlement Management Usercube creates an exhaustive and reliable catalog of the entitlements available in the managed systems and fulfills the right assignments to the right users.</description></item><item><title>Further Reading</title><link>http://localhost/posts/Further-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 17:42:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/Further-reading/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tutorial - Training steps</title><link>http://localhost/posts/tutorial/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:35:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/tutorial/</guid><description>Installation of the USERCUBE Demo Latest Version In order to use USERCUBE on your local device, you need to realise an installation on premise. You follow the steps below:
You first look for the latest version of the USERCUBE server on the Pipelines page. You download the three bottom folders : Runtime, SDK and SQL. On your computer C:\UsercubeDemo, you delete everything except Sources and Runtime folders.</description></item><item><title>Connectors</title><link>http://localhost/posts/Connectors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 17:16:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/Connectors/</guid><description>How to Create Connectors from the User Interface On the Home page of the USERCUBE server, there is a Connectors button.
You click on this button and you see all existing connectors. To create a new one, you click on + New.
You fill the information. In this example, we want to call our connector AD_TEST. We give the same name in English(US). We choose a local agent.</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>http://localhost/posts/hugo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 14:37:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo is a software that helps write in Go language in order to build blogs and static sites and put them online. It is a software that combines files to turn them into HTML, CSS and JavaScript files.
With Hugo you write in Markdown, which is a markup language easier to use than HTML.
These are the steps to build a new website:
You create a folder to store your future website.</description></item><item><title>Html</title><link>http://localhost/posts/html/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 14:37:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/html/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tasks</title><link>http://localhost/posts/Tasks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 14:38:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/posts/Tasks/</guid><description>How to process tasks There are three types of tasks for the USERCUBE documentation: bugs ; features ; studies.
When you start working on a ticket, you first work on dev.azure:
You change the task state to Active. You create a branch called doc/XXXXX_aaaaaaa where XXXXX is the task number and aaaaaaa is the explicit name you decide to give it. Then you open GitExtensions:</description></item></channel></rss>